Every ending is a new beginning!
Crystal Skulls is a adventure, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Todor Chapkanov.
A millionaire philanthropist collects the famous Crystal
Skulls trying to tap into their ancient powers.
It is up to a team lead by a college professor whose father disappeared searching for the 13th skull to save the world
when the first 12 skulls are united and reek havoc on the earth without the control of the 13th skull.
John Winston, played by Richard Burgi.
Sienna, played by Wendy Glenn.
Mitchell, played by Sam Redford.
Hadden, played by David Rintoul.
Colonel Bailey, played by JR Esposito.
Terry, played by Matt Rippy.
Crystal skulls are human skull hardstone carvings made of clear, milky white or other types of quartz (also called "rock crystal"), claimed to be pre-Columbian
Mesoamerican artifacts by their alleged finders; however, these claims have been refuted for all of the specimens made available for scientific studies.
The results of these studies demonstrated that those examined were manufactured in the mid-19th century or
later, almost certainly in Europe, during a time when interest in ancient culture abounded.
The skulls appear to have been crafted in Germany, quite likely at workshops in the town of Idar-Oberstein, which
was renowned for crafting objects made from imported Brazilian quartz in the late 19th century.
Despite some claims presented in an assortment of popularizing literature, legends of crystal skulls with mystical
powers do not figure in genuine Mesoamerican or other Native American mythologies and spiritual accounts.
The skulls are often claimed to exhibit paranormal phenomena by some members of the
New Age movement, and have often been portrayed as such in fiction.
Crystal skulls have been a popular subject appearing in numerous science
fiction television series, novels, films, and video games.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and mind_bending.